zerotohundred.com 2012-06-12

# Privacy Policy - Zerotohundred.com

**Zerotohundred.com Privacy Statement**  
The following is the Privacy Statement for Zerotohundred.com  
Please read this statement regarding our website. If you have questions please ask us via our [contact form](http://www.zerotohundred.com/newforums/sendmessage.php).

**Forums/Classifieds/Comments/Message Boards**  
Zerotohundred.com contains comment sections within our Content, Classifieds and Forums section. We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce "comment spam." These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Email Addresses**  
Email adress are used during the membership registration and through our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share your email with any third party. We do do periodically send advertising via email via dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our [contact form](http://www.zerotohundred.com/sendmessage.php).

**Ownership of Information**  
Zerotohundred.com is the sole owner of any information posted on our website. Though we may not endorse all of them, we take pride in providing a constructive discussion venue for our users, which we have no intention of defaming any individual or organization.

**Cookies**  
We Currently assign cookies to our readers in order to manage their preferences and ensure the site's functionality. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Zerotohundred.com and its advertisers may also use ad network providers, such as Google Adsense, Text Link Ads, Innity, Ad Max, Pixel Media, to help present advertisements on Zerotohundred.com. These ad network providers use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience. Zerotohundred.com may share certain non-personally identifiable information about you as a Zerotohundred.com user (such as user age and postcode) with certain ad network providers, to help them deliver more relevant advertisements through their ad networks. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies, not that of Zerotohundred.com. 

**Traffic Reports**  
We use industry-standard traffic reporting records through our multiple website platforms, Google Analytics records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**  
We will make every possible effort to preserve user privacy but Zerotohundred.com may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**  
If Zerotohundred.com is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our website, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**  
Zerotohundred.com frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Zerotohundred.com.

**Notification of Changes**  
When Zerotohundred.com makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact form](http://www.zerotohundred.com/sendmessage.php).
